[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Shrek the Third Queen Lillian was voiced by Dame Judy Dench.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who does not belong to this list of high school dropouts: Julie Andrews, Marlon Brando, Johnny Depp, Demi Moore, Avril Lavigne, Christina Applegate, Jude Law, Leah Remini, John Travolta, Ed Norton.", "correct_answer": "Ed Norton", "incorrect_answers": ["Avril Lavigne", "Leah Remini", "Johnny Depp"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "True of False: Jules Vernes real name was Jean-Luc Vernes.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The dish called American fried rice is not in fact American. Where was it created?", "correct_answer": "Thailand", "incorrect_answers": ["China", "Italy", "France"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the main protein found in the egg white?", "correct_answer": "Ovalbumin", "incorrect_answers": ["Fibrin", "Gluten", "Phosphoprotein"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does actinology study?", "correct_answer": "The study of the effect of light on chemicals", "incorrect_answers": ["fruits and seeds", "clouds", "ants"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which set contains triangular numbers?", "correct_answer": "1, 3, 6, 10, 15, 21, 28", "incorrect_answers": ["1, 10, 100, 1000, 10000, 100000, 1000000", "1, 2, 3, 5, 7, 11, 13, 17", "1, 4, 9, 16, 25, 36, 49"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the color from the visible spectrum produced by waves of the smallest wavelength?", "correct_answer": "Violet", "incorrect_answers": ["Yellow", "Red", "Green"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Animator Walt Disney directed his first cartoon, Alice in Wonderland for this company.", "correct_answer": "Laugh - Gram Studios", "incorrect_answers": ["Loews Inc.", "Paramount", "Famous Players - Lasky"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was Aristotles teacher?", "correct_answer": "Plato", "incorrect_answers": ["Ptolemy", "Socrates", "Alexander"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This equation, Y=mX+B, represents what?", "correct_answer": "A line in the plane", "incorrect_answers": ["A prism", "A circle in the plane", "An ellipse in the plane"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "We all have learned that you can tell the age of a tree by the number of rings. Who was the first to discover this fact?", "correct_answer": "Leonardo Da Vinci", "incorrect_answers": ["Aristotle", "Luther Burbank", "Charles Darwin"]}]